ウェブリー・フォスベリー・オートマチック・リボルバー


非営利の使用であり、公序良俗や、関係する方々に迷惑をかけない限り

データを自分の責任で改造して使ってもかまいません。
自分で責任をとれる限り、改造したデータは配布してかまいません。元データの再配布はご遠慮ください。
ただし配布する場合、必ず同じ条件（非営利・改造可・改造データ再配布可）で、改造の履歴を記述して配布してください。

2016年9月29日　アサシンP


Only for noncommercial use, in respect for the right of all concerned and within the common courtesy, you may

MODIFY the model/accessory/motion data at your own risk and on your own responsibility
REDISTRIBUTE ONLY the MODIFIED model/accessory/motion data (NEVER the original) UNDER THE SAME CONDITIONS of this readme, with the history of modifications, at your own risk and on your own responsibility.
JUST IMAGINE all creators behind the data you downloaded, and let’s enjoy OUR happy creative life.

September.29.2015  AssassinP


連絡先
Address

*mail
bifuclubxm2010@gmail.com

*Twitter
@ruin1110